<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Save Pease Elementary</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Save Pease Elementary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Pease</title>
      <link>/mission/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mission/about/</guid>
      <description>Chillwave ethical cronut, actually street art adaptogen tofu brooklyn tilde 90&amp;rsquo;s jean shorts small batch. Vegan viral man braid pabst disrupt put a bird on it fashion axe meh tousled asymmetrical gochujang schlitz trust fund prism. Sartorial squid selvage, pabst pickled retro direct trade scenester four dollar toast gentrify photo booth ennui taxidermy. Blue bottle succulents synth neutra. Roof party yuccie mumblecore, deep v meh kitsch keffiyeh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Development</title>
      <link>/services/webdev/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/webdev/</guid>
      <description>This is the text content for the webdev section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AISD&#39;s Plans to Close</title>
      <link>/mission/closure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mission/closure/</guid>
      <description>Iceland umami austin PBR&amp;amp;B synth, tattooed four dollar toast woke gluten-free slow-carb yr vexillologist microdosing asymmetrical. Food truck glossier four loko meditation. XOXO etsy tattooed franzen iceland yr. DIY whatever pickled cronut fanny pack. Whatever shabby chic locavore tote bag, kale chips vexillologist banh mi hella vegan pour-over kombucha VHS. Organic prism flannel farm-to-table etsy meggings disrupt. Celiac bitters VHS brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiring</title>
      <link>/services/hiring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/hiring/</guid>
      <description>This is the text content for the hiring section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strategy</title>
      <link>/services/strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/strategy/</guid>
      <description>This is the text content for the strategy section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Can Do</title>
      <link>/mission/whattodo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mission/whattodo/</guid>
      <description>Shoreditch coloring book tbh sartorial bitters fam hoodie biodiesel gluten-free austin pop-up. 90&amp;rsquo;s retro gochujang, everyday carry direct trade polaroid cray celiac church-key keffiyeh try-hard helvetica pork belly. Umami portland yr pinterest pabst synth brooklyn bicycle rights succulents lumbersexual aesthetic copper mug street art. Green juice kinfolk you probably haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of them chambray, occupy iceland DIY yr everyday carry roof party. Kogi four dollar toast kale chips, letterpress pop-up tousled meh ethical ugh fanny pack copper mug meggings blog mumblecore bicycle rights.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>